[
    {
        "id": "1545266643668",
        "name": "First Game",
        "teams": [
            {
                "name": "Red Team",
                "score": 0
            },
            {
                "name": "Green Team",
                "score": 0
            }
        ],
        "categories": [
            {
                "name": "Cat 1",
                "tiles": [
                    {
                        "question": "Question 1",
                        "answer": "Answer 1",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 2",
                        "answer": "Answer 2",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 3",
                        "answer": "Answer 3",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 4",
                        "answer": "Answer 4",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 5",
                        "answer": "Answer 5",
                        "active": true
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "name": "Cat 2",
                "tiles": [
                    {
                        "question": "Question 1",
                        "answer": "Answer 1",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 2",
                        "answer": "Answer 2",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 3",
                        "answer": "Answer 3",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 4",
                        "answer": "Answer 4",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 5",
                        "answer": "Answer 5",
                        "active": true
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "name": "Cat 3",
                "tiles": [
                    {
                        "question": "Question 1",
                        "answer": "Answer 1",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 2",
                        "answer": "Answer 2",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 3",
                        "answer": "Answer 3",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 4",
                        "answer": "Answer 4",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 5",
                        "answer": "Answer 5",
                        "active": true
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "name": "Cat 4",
                "tiles": [
                    {
                        "question": "Question 1",
                        "answer": "Answer 1",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 2",
                        "answer": "Answer 2",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 3",
                        "answer": "Answer 3",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 4",
                        "answer": "Answer 4",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 5",
                        "answer": "Answer 5",
                        "active": true
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "name": "Cat 5",
                "tiles": [
                    {
                        "question": "Question 1",
                        "answer": "Answer 1",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 2",
                        "answer": "Answer 2",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 3",
                        "answer": "Answer 3",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 4",
                        "answer": "Answer 4",
                        "active": true
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Question 5",
                        "answer": "Answer 5",
                        "active": true
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
]
